### **ROBERT THOMPSON**

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER | HTML, CSS | MERN STACK

#### **DETAILS**

#### **ADDRESS**

Chicago, IL United States

#### PHONE

614-440-7141

#### **EMAIL**

rob.thomp15@gmail.com

#### LINKS

**GitHub** 

<u>Portfolio</u>

<u>LinkedIn</u>

SciPharm - Pharmacy

Website

SciPharm - Pharmacy

<u>Instagram</u>

#### SKILLS

Git, Github Version Control

HTML & CSS - Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Ulkit, Bulma

JavaScript & jQuery

React.js

Node.js - Inquirer, Express

MySQL & Sequelize ORM

MongoDB & Mongoose

Apollo GraphQL

Heroku

**CLI Troubleshooting** 

Object-Oriented Programming

Data Structures & Algorithms

#### **PROFILE**

I am a creative, full stack web developer with a background in health sciences and pharmacy. Through my coding experience, I developed a strong adaptability to new technologies, as well as strength in refactoring code and resolving bugs. During pharmacy school, I created an educational pharmacy website/ Instagram for my classmates and decided to transition into computer science to fulfill my web development passion. I completed the full stack coding boot camp at Northwestern where I learned how to create front, back-end, and full stack web applications.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

## Inpatient Pharmacy Intern, OhioHealth: Riverside Methodist Hospital

Columbus, OH

Columbus, OH

Jan 2021 — Aug 2022

- · Performed holistic Medication Reconciliation in the Emergency Department
  - Communicated important drug and patient information with prescribers and pharmacists
- Compounded sterile products utilizing aseptic technique in-line with USP-797 best practices
- Answered nurse and prescriber questions regarding IV compatibility, and drug administration

## Introductory Pharmacy Practice Experience (IPPE) Rotation, Kroger

Feb 2021 — May 2021

- Counseled patients on supplements, over the counter, and prescription medications
- Completed prescription transfers and took verbal medication orders from prescribers

### EDUCATION

# Fullstack Web Development Certificate, Northwestern University

Evanston, IL

Aug 2022 — Nov 2022

### Doctorate of Pharmacy (PharmD), Ohio State University

Columbus, OH

Aug 2020 — Feb 2022

Created & Designed Pharmacy infographic website that students utilize to retain Pharmacy School knowledge

Pharmacology, Medicinal Chemistry

### **B.S. Human Sciences, Ohio State University**

Columbus, OH

Aug 2015 — Dec 2018

# Secretary-Treasurer: Ohio State PharmD Class of 2024

Columbus

Aug 2020 — Feb 2022

- · Assisted Class President with any needs or concerns
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$  Took weekly meeting minutes and sent to class via email
- · Ran Class of 2024 apparel fundraiser